<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Source" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>JevisSelectData</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Node to connect and Search for data within jevis. 
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>This node creates a connector to an arbitrary JEVis Database and allows to search for data within the database. 
        You will need to connect with your connection information to jevis. Afterwards the node allows to conduct different kinds of searches. Searches are Datapoint Search with and without attributes, Nodetype Search and Structural Search. Only one tpye of search can be selected. 
        which will enable you to select your data. In the Output table you will get the data you searched for in a convenient way so you can filter that data again as you like and also see at one glance 
        the most important informations of the datapoint. 
        As long as you are disconnected from JEVis there are no further functions of any use.  </intro>
        
        
        <tab name="Configure Connection ">
            <option name="Hostaddress">Enter a valid host address for the JEVis database.</option>
            <option name="Port"> Enter here the port for the JEVis database. </option>
            <option name="SqlSchema"> Enter here the SQLschema for database connection. (This option is there because Jevis currently only allows a connection via SQL).</option>
            <option name="SqlUser">Enter here the user of for the SQL database. (This option is there because Jevis currently only allows a connection via SQL)</option>
            <option name="SqlPassword"> Enter here the the password of the SQL user. (This option is there because Jevis currently only allows a connection via SQL)</option>
            <option name="JevisUser"> Enter here your user of the JEVis Database. </option>
            <option name="JevisPassword"> Enter here the password of your JEVis Database user.</option>
            <option name="Connect"> Press button when information is filled in completely and you want to connect to JEVis. </option>
        </tab>
        <tab name="Attribute and Datapoint Search">
            <option name="Search for Datapoints"> If Enabled the search will focus on searching through the Levels. </option>
            <option name="Search for NodeType"> If enabled the Search will focus on a given Nodetype and gives you specific nodetype. </option>
            <option name="Override Attribute Filter"> if Enabled all datapoints will be in the output without any filtering after. </option>
            <option name="Project"> Select the Project for the search.</option>
            <option name="Location"> Select the Location for the search.</option>
            <option name="Component"> Select the component for the search.</option>
            <option name="Device"> Select the name of the Datapoint. </option>
            
            <option name="Search for Attributes"> Select one or more attributes to be searched for. Strings can be put in to filter also for specific Values. </option>
            <option name="Search for Nodetype"> Select the nodetype when Nodetype search is selected. </option>
        </tab>
        <tab name="Structure Search">
        	<option name="Enable Structure Search"> If enabled search after Structure will be done.</option>
        	<option name="Node ID"> Enter the JEVis Node ID for Structure Search. </option>
        	<option name="Parents"> If enabled the Parent of the given Node ID will be in the output. </option>
        	<option name="Children"> If enabled the Children of the given Node ID will be in the output table. </option>
        	<option name="Siblings"> If enabled the Siblings of the given Node ID will be found. </option>
        	<option name="All Children"> If enabled all Children beneath the given Node ID will be found. </option> 
        
        </tab>

    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="In-Port name">Description of first input port...</inPort>
        <!-- possibly more input ports here-->
        <outPort index="0" name="Out-Port name">Description of first output port...</outPort>
        <!-- possibly more output ports here-->
    </ports>    
    <views>
        <view index="0" name="name of first view">Description of first view...</view>
        <!--view index="1" name="name of second view">Description of second view...</view-->
    </views>
</knimeNode>
